Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 8 and District 8 Locals, 1936-1957 UE.4.1.8
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 8, 1.
  - District 8 Don Harris Outgoing Correspondence, April 8 - June 28, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Hospitalizations, May 8, 1952; 14.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Vouchers, May 8, 1952; 15.
    - Harris to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Negotiations, May 8, 1952; 16.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Finances, May 12, 1952; 17.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Organization, May 22, 1952; 18.
    - Harris to Fitzgerald Regarding Relations, May 23, 1952; 19.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Organization, May 23, 1952; 20.
    - Harris to John Gojack Regarding Finances, May 29, 1952; 21.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Lost Time, May 29, 1952; 22.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Elections, May 29, 1952; 23.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Elections, June 19, 1952; 24.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Finances, June 19, 1952; 25.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Organization, June 20, 1952; 26.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Elections, June 20, 1952; 27.
  - District 8 Don Harris Outgoing Correspondence, June 28 - August 20, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Harris to James Matles Regarding Publications, June 25, 1952; 1.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Elections, June 25, 1952; 2.
    - Harris to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Organization, June 27, 1952; 3.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Organization, June 27, 1952; 4.
    - Harris to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, June 30, 1952; 5.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Finances, June 30, 1952; 6.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Steel Strike, July 1, 1952; 7.
    - Harris to Fitzgerald Regarding Strike Vote, July 1, 1952; 8.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Report on Local 115, July 1, 1952; 9.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Staff Arrangements, July 3, 1952; 10.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Staff Vacations, July 7, 1952; 11.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Finances, July 7, 1952; 12.
    - Harris to Matles, July 14, 1952; 13.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Publications, July 17, 1952; 14.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding International Association of Machinsts Elections, July 21, 1952; 15.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Election Results, July 22, 1952; 16.
    - Harris to Matles, July 28, 1952; 17
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Oliver Negotiations, August 1, 1952; 18.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Staff Movement, August 1, 1952; 19.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Organization, August 18, 1952; 20.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Oliver Negotiations, August 18, 1952; 21.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Finances, August 19, 1952; 22.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Fighting Fund, August 20, 1952; 23.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Organization, August 20, 1952; 24.
  - District 8 Don Harris Outgoing Correspondence, August 21 - November 19, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Harris to James Matles Regarding Strike Action, August 21, 1952; 1.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding St. Louis Amendment, August 22, 1952; 2.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Charles City Negotiations, August 28, 1952; 3.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Strike Report, September 2, 1952; 4.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Election Agreement, September 5, 1952; 5.
    - Harris to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, September 5, 1952; 6.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding William Senter Bail, September 28, 1952; 7.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding National Strike Fund, September 28, 1952; 8.
    - Harris to James Price Regarding Finances, October 3, 1952; 9.
    - Harris to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Finances, October 6, 1952; 10.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Organization, October 17, 1952; 11.
    - Harris to Dave Ratner Regarding Mailing List, October 18, 1952; 12.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Bills, October 18, 1952; 13.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Finances, November 3, 1952; 14.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Fighting Fund, November 6, 1952; 15.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Newspaper Clippings, November 11, 1952; 16.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Organization, November 12, 1952; 17.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Finances, November 13, 1952; 18.
    - Harris to Charles Hobbie Regarding Strike Situation, November 13, 1952; 19.
    - Harris to Robert Logsdon Regarding Strike Sitution, November 13, 1952; 20.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Strike Situation, November 14, 1952; 21.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Organization, November 14, 1952; 22.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Organization, November 19, 1952; 23-24.
  - District 8 Don Harris Outgoing Correspondence, November 24, 1952 - February 27, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Harris to Janet Barish Regarding Finances, November 24, 1952; 1.
    - Harris to James Matles Regarding Finances, November 28, 1952; 2.
    - Harris to August VandeVoorde Regarding Strike Welfare Fund, November 28, 1952; 3.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Organization, December 7, 1952; 4.
    - Harris to Julius Emspak Regarding Strike Relief, December 5, 1952; 5.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Organization, December 8, 1952; 6.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Strike Fund, December 15, 1952; 7.
    - Harris to Janet Barish Regarding Travel Expenses, December 15, 1952; 8.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Finances, December 17, 1952; 9.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Finances, December 19, 1952; 10-12.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Audit of Local 109, December 19, 1952; 13.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Finances, December 22, 1952; 14.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Finances, December 23, 1952; 15.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Bills, December 29, 1952; 16.
    - Harris to Emma Meagher Regarding Information, December 30, 1952; 17.
    - Harris to Rachel Klausner Regarding Replacement, January 12, 1953; 18.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Credential Card, January 13, 1953; 19.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Figthing Fund, January 12, 1953; 20.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Fighting Fund, Januayr 16, 1953; 21.
    - Harris to Klausner Regarding List of Officers, January 16, 1953; 22.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Suspension Notice, January 16, 1953; 23.
    - Harris to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Meeting, January 25, 1953; 24.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Oliver Corp., February 18, 1953; 25.
    - Harris to Fitzgerald Regarding Meeting Arrangement, February 27, 1953; 26.
  - District 8 Don Harris Outgoing Correspondence, March 2 - September 9, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Harris to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Organization, March 2, 1953; 1.
    - Harris to Russ Nixon Regarding Information, March 14, 1953; 2.
    - Harris to James Matles Regarding Local 115, March 14, 1953; 3.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Loan Application, March 20, 1953; 4-6.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Funds, March 23, 1953; 7.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Resolutions, March 31, 1953; 8.
    - Harris to Lorette Hopke Regarding Publications, April 24, 1953; 9.
    - Harris to Florence Criley Regarding Publications, April 24, 1953; 10.
    - Harris to David Ratner Regarding Publications, April 28, 1953; 11.
    - Harris to Julius Emspak Regarding Robertson Schnuett Case, April 28, 1953; 12.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Organization, May 1, 1953; 13.
    - Harris to Fitzgerald Regarding Executive Board, May 14, 1953; 14.
    - Harris to Fitzgerald Regarding Organization, May 21, 1953; 15.
    - Harris to Racheal Klausner Regarding Information, June 17, 1953; 16.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Oliver Plant Officers, June 17, 1953; 17.
    - Harris to Charles Sterner Regarding Publications, June 18, 1953; 18.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Finances, June 19, 1953; 19-20.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Publications, June 19, 1953; 21.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Vacations, June 19, 1953; 22.
    - Harris Letter to Fitzgerald, August 26, 1953; 23-25.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Publications, September 9, 1953; 26.
  - District 8 Don Harris Outgoing Correspondence, October 12, 1953 - June 28, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Harris to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Convention, October 13, 1953; 1.
    - Harris to John Ingram Regarding Organization, October 27, 1953; 2.
    - Harris to Julius Emspak Regarding Audit, November 13, 1953; 3.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Meeting, November 13, 1953; 4.
    - Harris to President Eisenhower Regarding McCarthyism, November 18, 1953; 5.
    - Harris to Fitzgerald Regarding Information, November 24, 1953; 6.
    - Harris to Fitzgerald Regarding Executive Board Meeting, November 25, 1953; 7.
    - Harris to Fitzgerald Regarding Organization, December 1, 1953; 8.
    - Harris to Emma Meagher Regarding Newspaper Clippings, December 7, 1953; 9.
    - Harris to Sterling Neal Regarding Farm Labor Relations, December 22, 1953; 10.
    - Harris to James Matles Regarding Subsidy, December 30, 1953; 11-12.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Meeting, December 30, 1953; 13.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Credentials, January 5, 1954; 14.
    - Harris to Clyde Ellis Regarding Farm Labor Support, January 14, 1954; 15.
    - Harris to Fitzgerald Regarding Farm Labor Subsidy, January 14, 1954; 16.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Farm Labor Subsidy, Januayr 14, 1954; 17.
    - Harris to David Ratner Regarding Senate Committee, January 15, 1954; 18.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Stewards Meeting, Januayr 15, 1954; 19.
    - Harris to Ratner Regarding Vouchers, Januayr 20, 1954; 20.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Organization, February 25, 1954; 21.
    - Harris to Ernest DeMaio Regarding Meeting, February 19, 1954; 22.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Officer's Bond, February 25, 1954; 23.
    - Harris to John Pelnish Regarding Allis-Chalmer's Meeting, March 11, 1954; 24.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Organization, April 29, 1954; 25.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Organization, May 5, 1954; 26.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Organization, June 28, 1954; 27.
  - District 8 Don Harris Outgoing Correspondence, June 28, 1954 - February 24, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Harris to James Matles Regarding Organization, June 28, 1954; 1.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Organization, June 28, 1954; 2.
    - Harris to Janet Barish Regarding Finances, July 2, 1954; 3.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Organization, July 9, 1954; 4.
    - Harris to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Organization, July 14, 1954; 5.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Oliver Corporation Finances, August 10, 1954; 6.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Progress Report, August 13, 1954; 7.
    - Harris to Barish Regarding Finances, August 30, 1954; 8.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Strike Agreement, September 1, 1954; 9.
    - Harris to Julius Emspak Regarding Meeting, October 4, 1954; 10.
    - Harris to David Ratner Regarding Information, October 18, 1954; 11.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Meeting Minutes, October 19, 1954; 12.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Travel Expenses, November 3, 1954; 13.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Farmell Situation, November 12, 1954; 14.
    - Harris to Elis Swa Regarding Organization, December 6, 1954; 15.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Conference, December 23, 1954; 16.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Organizational Finances, January 28, 1955; 17.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Allis-Chalmers, February 7, 1955; 18-19.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Organization, February 24, 1955; 20.
    - Harris to Fitzgerald Regarding Organization, February 24, 1955; 21.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Organization, February 24, 1955; 22.
  - District 8 Don Harris Outgoing Correspondence, March 3 - November 19, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Harris to Julius Emspak Regarding Stewards Meeting, March 3, 1955; 1.
    - Harris to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Stewards Meeting, March 3, 1955; 2.
    - Harris to James Matles Regarding Stewards Meeting, March 3, 1955; 3.
    - Harris to Fitzgerald Regarding Finances, March 10, 1955; 4.
    - Harris to Fitzgerald Regarding Harvester Situation, March 30, 1955; 5-7.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Per Capita, March 30, 1955; 8-9.
    - Harris to Fitzgerald Regarding Organization, April 9, 1955; 10.
    - Harris to David Ratner Regarding Burns, April 14, 1955; 11.
    - Harris to Fitzgerald Regarding Executive Board Meeting, May 4, 1955; 12.
    - Harris to Fitzgerald Regarding Election Results, May 18, 1955; 13.
    - Harris to Julius Emspak Regarding Per Capita Tax, July 8, 1955; 14.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Meeting, July 20, 1955; 15.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Convention, September 28, 1955; 16.
    - Harris to Fitzgerald Regarding Organization, October 5, 1955; 17.
    - Harris to Fitzgerald Regarding Organization, October 17, 1955; 18-20.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Finances, November 19, 1955; 21.
    - Harris to Matles Regarding Staff Salary, November 19, 1955; 22-23.
    - Harris to Janet Barish Regarding Finances, Undated; 24.
    - Harris to Emspak Regarding Finances, Undated; 25.
  - District 8 Robert Logsden Incoming Correspondence, April 9, 1941, December 28, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Julius Emspak Regarding Mileage Plan, December 28, 1944; 1.
    - James Matles Regarding Strike Funds, April 9, 1941; 2.
  - District 8 Robert Logsden Outgoing Correspondence, August 18, 1937 - October 22, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Logsden to James Matles Regarding Agreements, August 18, 1937; 1.
    - Logsden to Matles Regarding Organization, September 28, 1937; 2.
    - Logsden to Julius Emspak Regarding Election Results, October 12, 1938; 3.
    - Logsden to Matles Regarding War Bonds, July 13, 1942; 4.
    - Logsden to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, January 3, 1943; 5.
    - Logsden to Emspak Regarding Organization, October 25, 1943; 6.
    - Logsden to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, October 27, 1943; 7.
    - Logsden to Emspak Regarding Organization, January 13, 1944; 8.
    - Logsden to Emspak Regarding Field Report, January 14, 1944; 9.
    - Logsden to Emspak Regarding Report, February 15, 1944; 10.
    - Logsden to Emspak Regarding Report, March 20, 1944; 11.
    - Logsden to Emspak Regarding Report, April 24, 1944; 12.
    - Logsden to Emspak Regarding Report, June 15, 1944; 13.
    - Logsden to Emspak Regarding Report, July 18, 1944; 14.
    - Logsden to Emspak Regarding Report, August 17, 1944; 15.
    - Logsden to Emspak Regarding Mileage Allowance, September 5, 1944; 16.
    - Logsden to National Staff Regarding Elections, October 16, 1944; 17.
    - Logsden to Emspak Regarding Report, January 10, 1945; 18.
    - Logsden to Emspak Regarding Mileage Report, January 15, 1945; 19.
    - Logsden to Emspak Regarding Organization, October 15, 1945; 20.
    - Logsden to Emspak Regarding Finances, February 6, 1945; 21.
    - Logsden to Matles Regarding Evansville Report, October 16, 1948; 22.
    - Logsden to Joseph Pogue Regarding Evansville Report, October 22, 1948; 23.
  - District 8 Robert Logsden Outgoing Correspondence, October 24, 1949 - June 22, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Logsden to Leroy Bartley Regarding Local 808 Charter, October 24, 1949; 1.
    - Logsden to James Matles Regarding Rock Falls, February 28, 1950; 2.
    - Logsden to Matles Regarding Expenses, March 2, 1950; 3.
    - Logsden to Matles Regarding Bills, November 24, 1950; 4.
    - Logsden to Julius Emspak Regarding Information, January 8, 1953; 5.
    - Logsden to Emspak Regarding Information, January 8, 1953; 6.
    - Logsden to Matles Regarding Allis Chalmers, July 11, 1953; 7.
    - Logsden to Matles Regarding Allis Chalmers, July 16, 1953; 8.
    - Logsden to William Senter Regarding Staff Arrangements, June 22, 1953; 9.
  - District 8 General Incoming Correspondence, 1938 - 1948 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Janet Barish Regarding Fringe Benefits, July 14, 1944; 1.
    - Barish Regarding Hospital Benefits, November 20, 1944; 2.
    - Barish Regarding Staff Wages, March 2, 1951; 3-4.
    - Barish Regarding Staff Wages, April 3, 1941; 5.
    - Barish Regarding Finances, May 29, 1947; 6.
    - Ernest Brawers Regarding Unpaid Bills, June 25, 1951; 7.
    - Lewis Berne Regarding Organization, February 10, 1943; 8.
    - Ruth Best Regarding Publications, June 4, 1948; 9.
    - John Brophy Regarding Information, April 7, 1938; 10.
    - Bill Cahn Regarding Publicity, September 9, 1947; 11.
    - Cahn Regarding Program, December 13, 1949; 12.
    - Grace Cane Regarding Information, October 23, 1941; 13.
    - James Carey Regarding Meeting, February 25, 1938; 14.
    - Carey Regarding Emerson Strike, March 7, 1938; 15.
    - Carey Regarding Letter to President Roosevelt, October 29, 1938; 16.
    - Bill Chambers Regarding Hospitilization, July 5, 1944; 17.
    - Rose Claiton Regarding Sunnich Affair, December 6, 1943; 18.
    - John Connolly Regarding Maytag Case, October 18, 1941; 19-20.
    - Victor Decavitch Regarding Meeting, July 3, 1942; 21.
    - Clarence DePorter Regarding Rent, January 31, 1950; 22.
    - Albert Eberhard Regarding Strike Action, October 28, 1948; 23.
    - Dwight Eisenhower Regarding the War Effort, Undated; 24.
    - A.P. Eberter Regarding Staff Organization, Undated; 25.
  - District 8 General Incoming Correspondence, December 22, 1936 - October 10, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Julius Emspak Regarding UE Activities, December 22, 1936; 1.
    - Emspak Regarding Constitution, May 24, 1937; 2.
    - Emspak Regarding Organization, May 26, 1937; 3.
    - Emspak Regarding Organization, May 29, 1937; 4.
    - Emspak Regarding Organization, September 30, 1937; 5.
    - Emspak Regarding Organization, November 3, 1937; 6.
    - Emspak Regarding Maytag Company, February 2, 1938; 7.
    - Emspak Regarding Allowance, August 5, 1940; 8.
    - Emspak Regarding Mailing List, September 13, 1940; 9.
    - Emspak Regarding Strike Assistance, September 19, 1940; 10.
    - Emspak Regarding Per Capita, October 15, 1951; 11.
    - Emspak Regarding New Member Applications, October 21, 1940; 12.
    - Emspak Regarding Per Capita, October 15, 1940; 13.
    - Emspak Regarding Mailing List, October 17, 1940; 14-15.
    - Emspak Regarding Mailing List, October 21, 1940; 16.
    - Emspak Regarding Application Cards, October 21, 1940; 17.
    - Emspak Regarding Per Capita Application, October 30, 1940; 18.
    - Emspak Regarding Mailing List, Ocotber 31, 1940; 19.
    - Emspak Regarding Mailing List, November 12, 1940; 20.
    - Emspak Regarding Mailing List, December 10, 1940; 21-23.
    - Emspak Regarding Information, Januayr 13, 1941; 24.
    - Emspak Regarding Evansville Organization, April 2, 1941; 25.
    - Emspak Regarding Convention, July 13, 1941; 26.
    - Emspak Regarding Mrs. Buckley, July 21, 1941; 27.
    - Emspak Regarding Mailing List, October 4, 1941; 28-29.
    - Emspak Regarding Mailing List, October 10, 1941; 30.
  - District 8 General Incoming Correspondence, October 15, 1943 - November 10, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Julius Emspak Regarding Organization, October 15, 1943; 1.
    - Emspak Regarding Staff Salary, November 1, 1943; 2.
    - Emspak Regarding Organization, February 9, 1944; 3.
    - Emspak Regarding Phone Bill, March 16, 1944; 4.
    - Emspak Regarding Expenses, August 21, 1944; 5.
    - Emspak Regarding Lost Time, August 27, 1944; 6.
    - Emspak Regarding Mileage Arrangements, February 2, 1945; 7-8.
    - Emspak Regarding Mileage Expenses, February 2, 1945; 9.
    - Emspak Regarding Staff Movement, September 21, 1945; 10.
    - Emspak Regarding Expenses, July 10, 1945; 11.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances, August 2, 1945; 12.
    - Emspak Regarding Refund, January 31, 1946; 13.
    - Emspak Regarding Organization, May 8, 1947; 14.
    - Emspak Regarding Refund for Expenses, February 10, 1948; 15.
    - Emspak Regarding Evansville Budget, October 5, 1948; 16.
    - Emspak Regarding Organization, December 2, 1948; 17.
    - Emspak Regarding Organization, March 30, 1949; 18.
    - Emspak Regarding Travel Expenses, May 11, 1949; 19.
    - Emspak Regarding Organization, September 14, 1949; 20.
    - Emspak Regarding Organization, December 22, 1949; 21.
    - Emspak Regarding Loan, February 21, 1951; 22.
    - Emspak Regarding Salary, October 7, 1952; 23.
    - Emspak Regarding Friends, September 29, 1953; 24-25.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances, September 29, 1953; 26.
    - Emspak Regarding Subsidy Check, November 10, 1953; 27.
    - Emspak Regarding Organization, Undated; 28.
  - District 8 General Incoming Correspondence, January 24, 1936 - October 2, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - E. P. Epping Regarding Arkansas Organization, January 4, 1943; 1.
    - Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Elections, December 10, 1945; 2.
    - Fitzgerald Regarding Election, December 10, 1945; 3.
    - Fitzgerald Regarding Information, January 9, 1946; 4.
    - Fitzgerald Regarding Convention, February 25, 1946; 5.
    - Fitzgerald Regarding Dues, April 10, 1947; 6.
    - Fitzgerald Regarding Meeting, March 21, 1950; 7.
    - Allan Haywood Regarding Memphis Organizaiton, November 1, 1944; 8.
    - Ralph Hetzel Regarding Jennie Jones, January 8, 1941; 9.
    - Leo Jandreau Regarding Organization, November 30, 1943; 10.
    - Jandreau Regarding Organization, December 1, 1943; 11.
    - Jandreau Regarding Organizaiton, December 4, 1943; 12.
    - Ray Klausner Regarding Quarterly Audits, October 2, 1953; 13.
    - John Kamps Regarding Buajrus-Eric Corporation, October 28, 1948; 14.
    - Morris Levin Regaridng Attorney Bill, January 9, 1941; 15.
    - C. Merritt Regarding Sentner Case, January 17, 1941; 16-17.
    - Robert Mason Regarding Report on Strikes, July 24, 1936; 18.
  - District 8 General Incoming Correspondence, April 7, 1939 - January 25, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - James Matles Regarding Convention, April 7, 1939; 1.
    - Matles Regarding Staff Movement, September 16, 1939; 2.
    - Matles Regarding Organization, July 22, 1940; 3-4.
    - Matles Regarding Staff Movement, September 12, 1941; 5.
    - Matles Regarding Organization, October 31, 1941; 6.
    - Matles Regarding Minn-Molin Organization, November 14, 1941; 7.
    - Matles Letter, December 31, 1941; 8.
    - Matles Regarding Meeting, July 6, 1942; 9.
    - Matles Regarding Victor Pasehe, February 19, 1943; 10.
    - Matles Regarding Strike Action, January 8, 1946; 11.
    - Matles Regarding Organization, April 1, 1946; 12.
    - Matles Regarding Publicity, September 26, 1947; 13.
    - Matles Regarding Termination of Appointment, September 26, 1947; 14.
    - Matles Regarding Wagner Electric Corporation, June 15, 1948; 15.
    - Matles Regarding Organization, October 14, 1948; 16.
    - Matles Regarding Staff Negotiation, January 12, 1949; 17-18.
    - Matles Regarding Finances, November 19, 1949; 19.
    - Matles Regarding Finances, June 29, 1950; 20.
    - Matles Regarding Travel Allowance, June 30, 1950; 21.
    - Matles Regarding Evansville Seeger Corporation, January 10, 1952; 22.
    - Matles Regarding Finances, April 21, 1953; 23.
    - Matles Regarding Vacation, June 4, 1953; 24.
    - Matles Regarding December Per Capita, January 25, 1954; 25.
  - District 8 General Incoming Correspondence, August 14, 1937 - February 17, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Irving Meyers Regarding Outstanding Bill, April 1, 1953; 1.
    - Sherly Miller Regarding Printing Bills, July 26, 1950; 2.
    - William Mitchell Regarding Organization, December 7, 1937; 3.
    - Mitchell Regarding Information, April 13, 1938; 4.
    - L. Moffot Regarding Charter, October 12, 1938; 5.
    - Russ Nixon Regarding Organization, February 18, 1943; 6.
    - Joseph Pogue Regarding Seeger Negotiation, July 2, 1949; 7.
    - D.A. Price Regarding Suttle Employment, January 22, 1938; 8.
    - David Ratner Regarding Employee Assignments, February 12, 1947; 9.
    - Ratner Regarding Finances, June 17, 1947; 10.